Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
[rock music playing]
[music stops]
Warning. The stunts
in this movie were
performed by professionals.
so for your safety
and the protection of
those around you.
do not attempt any of the
stunts you're about to see.
[Jason] That look all right?
[Johnny] Just turn it up.
here. turn it up.
[Jason] See? It's recording.
-[Johnny] Okay.
-[Jason] And then
[Johnny] Should I wear
my glasses for this?
[Jeff] It'll it'll be okay.
[Jason] Go ahead.
Well. I'm Johnny Knoxville.
United States of America.
and I'll be doin'
a little article
on self-defense equipment.
We're goin' to drive out
to the desert and
I have a .38 hammerless
nice and light
Smith and Wesson.
that's got all the stopping
power of a nine millimeter.
And I'll be gettin' shot
in the chest
with this 911
level IIA Kevlar vest.
Oh. and. to absorb some
of the impact from the bullet.
I'll be putting
these magazines.
couple of Hustlers
and a couple of Leg Worlds.
under the vest
to avoid any and all
blunt-force trauma.
All right.
That's why I'd rather have
someone else shoot me.
-[Loomis]
fuckin' sketch. man.
-[Jeff] Hang on a sec.
Like that. Jason?
[Jason] Uh. looks pretty good.
[Jason]
I can't handle this. dude.
[Loomis] Dude.
it's fuckin' sketch. man.
[Loomis]
Dude. don't be stupid.
[Jason] Say a prayer. dude.
This is beyond dumb.
-Let's fuckin' go.
-[gun chamber clicks]
[Jason] Now you gotta go
the whole way around.
-You sure?
-[Jason] I can't handle this.
[Loomis]
P.J.. let's fucking go.
[Jason] Find out
where the bullet went.
-[Loomis] P.J.
-[gun chamber clicks]
[Loomis] Come on. man!
-P.J.. let's fucking go.
-[gun chamber clicks]
[Loomis] I'm about to throw a
fuckin' rock at you. Let's go.
-[gun chamber clicks]
-[Jason] It's the next one.
[Loomis] P.J.. come on!
[Jason] I can't handle this.
[Loomis] Make sure
you got it fuckin'
P.J.
This is so fuckin' lame. I
can't even tell you right now.
Forget it.
-[gunshot]
-[grunts]
-[Johnny] Let's go.
-[Loomis chuckles]
[Jason]
Let's go. dude. Just go.
Put it in the thing and go.
Didn't hurt?
No. I was kinda scared though.
See? Didn't even
leave a fucking--
Dude. I told you guys.
[Jason]
Look at the powder burn.
[Johnny] I know.
Yeah. I was shaking a little.
You guys wanna go watch it
on the TV?
[Jason] Fuck yeah.
["Holding Out for a Hero"
plays]
[grunts]
[grunts. groans]
[crackling]
[Rachel yells]
[Spike]
Smile. this is gonna be great.
Walk away. back away.
back away. back away.
back away.
-Ow! Ow. fuck! Ow. fuck!
-[screaming]
Fuck!
[screams]
[Wee Man grunts]
[Ehren groans]
Hello. I'm Johnny Knoxville.
Welcome to Jackass.
Oh! Ow!
-[laughter]
-[Johnny groans]
-[screams]
-[laughter]
Whoa. whoa! Okay. okay!
["Corona" playing]
-[groans]
-[laughter]
[whistling]
[screams]
[screaming]
Oh. no. no. no. no. no.
[grunts]
-[thudding]
-[groans]
[cheering]
[screaming]
[Ryan] Fuck!
[Steve-O] Oh. fuck!
Welcome to the first day
of our final film.
[Spike]
So what are you feeling?
Uh. I'm sad.
[Spike] How come?
I guess. uh
a big part of my.
our life is
almost over.
[Spike]
Does it make you sad. Chris?
No. I'm not in touch
with my emotions.
[laughter]
So we have a new Jackass
cast member.
His name's 1W-Larry.
He's a humanoid robot.
And voicing that robot
is Mr. Adam Ray.
And you're going to be
making history today
with the first robot-to-human
prostate exam.
This is what Jackass
looks like at 50. I guess.
[laughing]
-We are of that age
-Damn good. though.
where we have
to get prostate exams.
-Yes. this is
raising awareness.
-And so we hired the finest.
[Adam] You see
the finger on that thing?
[Steve-O] I did.
Yeah. that's not a finger.
by the way.
It's a claw.
You're going to run into some
trouble around mid-finger.
It's not there. It's this side
that's all sharp.
[Johnny] How many times
have you done this. Larry?
[in robotic voice]
Maybe "letting it rip" is
a bad choice of words. Larry.
I'm Steve-O. and prostate
health is super important.
So. this is
the robot rectal exam.
[Larry] Yadda. yadda. yadda.
-[Steve-O] They're off.
-[Chris] Stay safe.
[Steve-O]
Non-lubricated condoms.
[Johnny] No. we have lube.
Oh. my God. it's so sharp.
Here. I'm just gonna put
a little lube on for you.
Crunchy peanut butter.
-[Ehren] Oh. no.
-[Steve-O] Why crunchy?
Drop the laundry.
Oh. my God.
[crew groaning]
[Chris] Oh. gross!
[Larry]
Wait. wait. wait.
[Wee Man] Slow down. Larry.
[Larry] Wait. wait. wait.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
Wait. Wait.
[Chris]
There we go. there we go!
[Steve-O screams]
-[laughter]
-[screaming continues]
[Chris] Spread 'em out!
Steve-O. spread 'em out!
Spread those cheeks out!
Somebody help him.
[Larry]
[Chris] Steve!
Is your chocolate
in his peanut butter
or his peanut butter
in your chocolate?
[Larry]
[Chris]
We need more peanut butter.
[Larry]
[Johnny] Oh. my God!
[Wee Man] There we go!
[Larry]
[Chris] You're almost
almost there.
[screaming]
That's it. That's it.
[Ehren] Breathe. Go. Larry!
Get down!
[Larry]
[screaming]
-[laughter]
-[Ehren] Lean over.
[Larry]
[Ehren] Oh. my God.
Hey. Larry.
let Lance smell your finger.
[Larry]
[Ehren]
Lookit. it's not that bad.
[gags]
[Larry] Yep. Yep. Yep.
[retching]
[Chris]
Not on your damn camera!
[Larry]
[Ehren] I'll help you.
-Okayhere we go.
-I got you.
[Larry]
I got you. I got you.
-[Larry vocalizing]
-[Steve-O screaming]
[Ehren] Don't move!
[Larry]
Okay. let go. Larry.
Let go. Larry.
[Larry]
Larry. let go! let go!
He's got his dick all the way!
Oh. my God!
Oh. my God! Oh. shit!
[Chris] Oh. my God. dude.
[Larry]
[laughter]
Thank you. Thank you.
Good job. Steve-O.
Thanks. guys.
[Larry]
Can I ask a question?
[Jeff] Yeah.
Why is this the last movie?
[laughs]
Well. I can't ride red rockets
or bulls anymore.
so it felt like
the natural place to stop.
Yeah. I'm certainly not gonna
ride those rockets.
Or the bulls. [chuckles]
You know.
we were talking. it's like
you know.
we got all this footage
no one's seen before
or barely seen.
and we can pick
our all-time favorite bits.
and. uh.
shoot some new footage
and I'll get to see
the warhammer again.
Well. if a scene requires me
to get into my birthday suit.
the answer
just might be yes.
[laughter]
Okay. this is called
the "Golf Course Airhorn."
When people tee off.
when they're coming down
with their swing.
we're going to blow
these airhorns.
[airhorn blares]
[Johnny] Oh. [sputters]
-[airhorn blares]
-[Johnny laughs]
-[Ehren] Here she goes again.
-[Dave] No. Is it another one?
-[airhorn blares]
-[Johnny laughs]
[Dave] She still hit it
really good.
[airhorn blares]
[Johnny laughing]
What'd I tell you?
I told you
I was gonna kick your ass.
[Johnny] Here.
you've lost your club. Sorry.
Didn't I tell you
I was gonna come over here
and kick your ass for that?
What? I'm sorry.
I got bursitis.
-[golfer] You got bursitis?
-[Johnny] Yeah.
-[golfer] So that means
you gotta play with a horn?
-[Johnny] It helps.
[golfer] I'll give you
something to play with. pal.
[Johnny] Sorry.
it won't happen again.
[giggling]
[whispering]
Oh. he's gonna fucking--
He took his glove. He threw--
[airhorn blares]
[Johnny] Oh. fuck.
[Dave] Shit. he's teein' off.
He's teein' off! Get down!
[Johnny] Oh. shit.
[laughter]
[Dave] Get back.
-Get down! Get down!
-[Johnny]
Watch this. wait. wait.
-Get down. Dimitri!
-[Johnny] Wait.
[airhorn blares]
[laughter]
[Dave] Oh. fuck.
Hello. my name's
Johnny Knoxville.
This is Tory Belleci.
international scientist.
This is "Follow the Leader."
So what's gonna happen is
Knoxville's gonna move his arm
and an electrical signal
will go into the computer.
and then he will be able
to control your arms.
-What?
-So. all you need to do
is flex your muscle.
No problem.
Yeah.
-[screams]
-[laughter]
All right.
-[Rachel] Oh. my God.
-Holy shit!
-What?
-[Dark Shark] Dude.
What the heck?
That's a lotta electroids!
Can we get Poopies
a coffee. please?
How hot is that coffee?
Hot.
Have a little bit of coffee.
Poopies. I'm sure it'll be--
-[laughter]
-[machine buzzing]
I think somebody
needs to shave.
-Here is a
-[Dark Shark] Gotta shave.
[Johnny] almost-new shaver.
Couple of weeks old.
Just start shaving.
-You gotta get--
-[Johnny] All you gotta--
Yeah. that's good.
-That's good.
-You missed a spot. yeah?
[screams]
[laughter]
Lance. why are you not--
Look. Lance is not looking.
Hey. Poopies.
you gotta get it underneath.
I know what you want
me to do. and
-I'll do it.
-[laughter]
Yeah. yeah. doing good.
Oh. my God.
[Dark Shark] Get the middle.
Get the middle.
-[machine buzzes]
-[laughter]
[Rachel] It looks so graceful.
-[Johnny groans]
-[Dark Shark] Oh!
[Johnny]
That was a close shave.
Zach does not. as of yet.
have a tattoo from me.
Oh. okay. well. let's do Zach.
And what tattoo
are you giving?
I'm gonna give Zach a nice.
nipple smiley face.
-That's a beautiful canvas.
-[machine buzzes]
[screams]
I mean. if you want me to have
the fuckin' art on there
Why're you yelling at me?
I would like this
to come out good.
Me. too. I'm on your side.
-I promise. hand to my heart.
-[screaming]
Okay. don't mess this up.
Steve-O.
Steady hand.
-Sorry.
-Okay.
[Steve-O straining]
-[screams]
-[laughter]
[Tory]
He can't get it centered.
That wasn't even close.
I'm not doin' it yet.
-[Steve-O] Okay.
-I'm not doin' it yet.
-I'm doing it!
-[screams]
You fucking--
[Dark Shark]
You got it. Steve-O!
Steve-O! Steve-O!
Steve-O! Steve-O! Steve-O!
-[Steve-O groaning. straining]
-[chanting continues]
[Rachel] It's good.
It looks good. It looks good.
It looks good.
How did that feel?
Not good.
[Johnny] Holy shit.
[Tory] Hey. Zach.
it's pretty awesome. dude.
[Johnny] Oh. my God!
-Great job. Poopies.
-Thank you.
Great job. Tory.
Thanks. Steve-O.
And Zach.
And thank God
Bunny the Lifeguard's here
to make everything safe.
-Thank you.
-Yeah. I-- I really don't--
I still don't understand why
they asked for a lifeguard
on duty. but
it's better to have one
and not need him
than need him
and not have him.
Well. the. the convict bit
we've always wanted
to include in our movies.
We shot it for the pilot of
the TV show and got shut down.
Our crew member got arrested.
MTV couldn't shoot in
West Hollywood for ten years.
So no one's really seen it.
It's been sitting there
for 25 years.
It was total chaos.
Today. I'm going to be
an escapee
from the LA County Jail
and go into a hardware store
and see if they'll lend me
a hacksaw.
Ow.
[Spike] I see the lens.
[cameraman] Okay. Good.
Do I need some dirt
on my face?
[Jeff] Try and get up closer
to him.
[Spike] He needs some
on his neck. too.
Is my shirt too--?
Ah. that's good.
[Spike] Should we
slap you around?
Yeah. that helps. Thanks.
[panting]
[cashier] Okay.
[cashier] Let me get
somebody. okay?
[grunts]
[thud. clanking]
-[clanking]
-[Johnny grunts]
[panting]
[metal scraping]
Help me!
[Spike] Excuse me.
what's going on?
[rapid scraping]
[Johnny] Someone help me!
We're kind of closed
for right now.
We're not letting anybody in.
[straining]
[Spike]
He's probably an escapee
from the jail or somewhere.
Handcuffed in
a sheriff's jumpsuit?
[Johnny] Get outta my way.
[Johnny]
[Jeff] Fuck!
[Spike] What? Oh. fuck me.
-[Jeff] Oh. fuck.
-[Spike] Oh. shit. no way.
[officer shouts]
[Spike] What should we do?
[Jeff] Dude.
-[officer] Get on the ground.
-[Jeff] Keep filmin'. dude.
[officer] Copy that.
[Johnny] I have
a good explanation for this.
[officer] How come
you're not in jail?
[Johnny]
'Cause I don't belong there.
How did you get out?
[Johnny]
I was never in jail.
[officer]
What is this in the back?
-That's a microphone.
-From what?
Cause we're. ah. filming.
You're filming?
Yes. ma'am.
That is really stupid!
[cameraman]
[Johnny] We didn't mean
to cause a ruckus.
You're wearing an LA county
jumpsuit with handcuffs on.
what do you think?
Yeah. I guess I wasn't
thinking. too. I apologize.
You got a camera on you?
-Is it off?
-[cameraman] It's on.
It's on? Are you filming this?
[officers] Turn it off!
So. upon arrival today.
we were informed
by Mr. Cliver that
our production manager
informed us
we are on
officially on hiatus.
A kind of suspension because
of the incident yesterday
at the hardware store.
But I guess this show
may get to air. it may not.
[Jeff chuckles]
But
-Have anything to add. Jeff?
-[Jeff] I do not.
I think let's just think
about the poo cocktail today.
Right. We're focusing
on the poo cocktail.
[Jeff] Yeah.
My name is Johnny Knoxville.
and this is
the "Poo Cocktail."
[yelling]
[Johnny] I think it's about
ten years ago today
that I was doin'
the first Poo Cocktail.
and now you're
taking the reins
and taking it to
a whole other level.
I'm Steve-O. and this is
the "Poo Cocktail Supreme."
[Johnny laughs]
All right. Good luck.
[lock clicking]
[Chris] You ready. Steve-O?
No.
[sighs]
[Chris] Order up!
Poo Cocktail Supreme!
[thud]
[team members shouting]
[laughing and shouting]
Oh. shit!
[screaming]
[team members groaning]
[thumping. liquid spraying]
[Steve-O vomiting]
[laughing] He's puking.
[gagging]
Dude. it fuckin' reeks. man!
[Johnny] What is.
what's wrong with you. Bam?
[team members talking]
[Johnny] Are you okay.
Steve-O?
[Ryan] Oh. my God.
It's gonna be ugly. I don't
know if you wanna see this.
-[laughing]
-[Chris] Oh. my God.
[Johnny] Oh. Jesus!
-[Jeff] Oh. my God.
-[Chris] Oh. my God.
[Johnny] Help him
out of there.
-[Jeff] Let him out!
-[Chris] Oh. my God.
[laughter]
[team member] Oh!
[laughter continuing]
[Ryan yells]
-Look at him!
-Oh. my God.
[Johnny] Jump in that lake
right now.
[Ryan] The worst damn thing
you can imagine.
[Jeff] Oh. my God.
[Johnny] Oh. my God.
[laughter]
[Wee Man retching]
[Dave retching]
Jesus!
Yeah. dude.
That was rad.
It went so high.
It was so scary.
[Chris] This is the kind of
extreme shit
that those extreme dudes
don't even think of.
[slowed-down screaming]
[Chris] I mean.
that had it all.
That had danger. it had shit.
It had puke.
Yeah. that's what
this show's all about.
And sex appeal.
[both laughing]
[Johnny] Do it!
-[screams]
-[all] Oh!
[Johnny] Jesus Christ.
What an idiot.
[others laughing]
[Larry]
Hey. Larry!
[Johnny] Where you been?
[Larry]
-[Poopies] He's drunk.
-[Johnny] He's had
a couple of drinks.
He's a little wobbly
right now.
We're about to give Poopies
lip injections
to make him 23% more gorgeous.
[Larry]
[Ehren] Oh. my gosh!
He got you!
Hello. Dr. Julie.
-Hello.
-[Poopies] Hi.
This is Poopies. and we want
to make him more handsome
with some lip injections.
-Can you help us?
-Yes.
Holy shit. Are you serious?
So. during this whole movie.
I'm gonna have
the biggest lips.
[Johnny] You're gonna have
the most beautiful lips.
-Full lips.
-Full.
-[Poopies] Oh. my God.
-Volumptious.
I'm Poopies.
and this is "Lip Filler."
[Johnny laughs]
Okay. normally.
people get numbing. but
Normally people get numbing.
-No. you don't need it.
-No?
-No. no numbing.
-Okay. Just relax.
[Adam] What is this
you're putting in?
-This is hyaluronic acid.
-[Adam] Oh. this is it.
[Larry]
-[Wee Man] Don't move. either.
-[Dark Shark]
That's a long-ass needle.
-[Wee Man] Stay still.
-[Johnny] Oh. my God. [groans]
[Rachel] You're gonna get
so much work after this.
-[others exclaiming]
-Shit!
-[Larry]
-[others cheering]
-[Johnny] Now we're doin' good.
-[Rachel] Oh. my God!
All right.
-Yeah!
-Holy shit!
[Larry]
[Johnny] All right.
we can go bigger.
[Larry]
-[Johnny] You can go bigger.
-[Rachel laughing]
[Dr. Julie] Now we're gonna
do the bottom.
[Dark Shark] Damn! I thought
that was about it.
Dude. what the fuck
is this shit?
You look awesome. Poopies.
Is it supposed to have
the right side be bigger?
[Larry]
I think I can probably put
just a little bit more
and that's it.
-[Jasper] Sexy is the word.
-[Ehren] Oh. fuck.
it's turning white!
What the fuck?
I look more like one of those
botched fucking housewives.
[Larry]
Yeah.
-[laughter]
-Oh. fucking Larry.
They're all lumpy and shit.
[Chris] I think it looks good.
[Johnny] All right!
Way to go. Poopies.
-[Rachel] Yeah. you're good.
-[Johnny] Yeah!
[team member]
What are you pouting at?
On Jackass Forever.
Knoxville and I
are just interviewing
the new guys
and straight up. like.
"Poopies. are you afraid
of anything?"
He's like.
"Well. I'll tell you what.
I don't like the dark.
and I don't like--"
You know. just like
layin' it all out. Like
But I don't think Bam
ever told us
he was scared of snakes.
We just kinda happened to
figure it out
when snakes came out.
Once we figured that out.
it sure wrote a lot of bits.
You know. the worse
the experience is
the better it looks
on screen.
[Jeff laughing]
So. today we're going to
bring the cast
into this room. two at a time.
to shoot a rattlesnake stunt.
But that's just a ruse
to get them in here.
so we can lock the door.
turn out the lights
and make their life
a living hell.
This is
"Silence of the Lambs."
[Johnny chuckles]
-[rattling]
-You hear that?
[Jeff] What is it?
-That's a rattlesnake.
-[Jeff] No. it isn't.
It is. Listen.
-[Jeff] Oh. really?
-Jules.
[Jeff] But you're not
a part of this bit.
[Johnny]
You're in peanut gallery.
He's got a western
diamondback rattlesnake.
He's gonna release it
on the ground.
Pontius is gonna take a cookie
and set it on its head.
and then I'm going to try
and take the cookie
off its head.
And this is a western
diamondback rattlesnake.
He's about five feet
and change.
Very. very venomous.
He will bite you
if you get too close.
and he will kill you.
Or try to.
-I'm not kidding.
-Whoa.
-Ready?
-[Bam] I'm gonna sit back.
Chris.
you're fucking nuts. man.
[Ehren] Whoa. shit. dude.
[rattling]
-[Jeff] Oh. fuck.
-[Bam] Dude!
-[Bam] Oh. my God.
[Chris] It's got a big head.
though.
[Johnny] Jesus!
[Chris] They can strike
so fast.
[Jules] He will absolutely
kill you. son.
at two heartbeats per second.
Can you feel my heart?
[others laughing]
Wow. dude!
[Jeff] All right.
It's goin' as fast as
that rattlesnake.
[Jeff] That's why
I won't do this.
I'm really scared for Johnny
right now.
[Jeff] All right.
let's put the snake away
and get these guys mic''d.
It's time to do this.
[Ehren] They're huge. man.
Those are big-ass snakes.
All right. switch the bucket.
Let's get the snake
out of the room.
[Poopies] Is there
an antidope here?
[tech 1] Okay. let's get
Knoxville for me.
That is what it's called.
Antivenom. not antidope.
What's antidope mean?
I don't even know.
[crew members shouting]
What's antidope?
[laughing] Uh. that's like--
-[door slams]
-[Zach] Oh. my fucking God.
-[Poopies] No!
-[Zach] No!
-[door slams]
-[Preston] Goddamn!
[Wee Man] Oh. fuck you. guys.
Wait. how-- Why are we
the only ones in here now?
I don't know. dude.
-[door slams]
-[Ehren] Doggone it!
[tech 1] Oh. fuck this.
let's go!
-He's driving himself around?
-[door slams]
[Bam] Oh. no! No!
[Johnny] Hello. my name's
Johnny Knoxville.
Welcome to hell.
[Bam] Please. no!
Wait. dude.
where's the fuckin' light?
Bam. seriously. there's
a snake in that bucket.
so don't fucking swing around.
Well. where should I go?
What am I gonna do?
Oh. fuck!
So. if we get bit. we die.
[Zach] Yeah. oh. God!
Are you serious?
Why the fuck did we go down
to the basement? [shrieks]
Dude. come on.
[Wee Man] Knox. what the fuck?
Come on.
Dude. Come on.
-[Wee Man screams]
-[Preston shrieks]
What the fuck?
[Ehren] I'm gonna break
that fucking door down.
[Dave] Do it. Ehren.
Did they just-- [screams]
[Ehren] Fuck this shit!
Ah. fuck you guys!
All right.
knock over the bucket
and cue the snake sound.
[Johnny] Oh. shit!
-[thudding]
-[rattling sound]
-[Johnny] Oh. shit.
-Oh. my God!
[Johnny] Everyone. stay--
Guys. stay on the couch.
The fuckin' snake.
-Bam.
-Yeah?
You gotta be cool. man.
there's a fuckin' snake
in here.
-[Bam] Yo. I don't know
what to do.
-[Johnny] Stay where you are.
-[Bam] All right.
-[rattling continuing]
[Bam screams]
Dude. it bit me. I think.
[Johnny] Jeff. Bam got bit!
No fuckin' shit.
[laughing]
-[rattling continuing]
-[Bam] I can't do it.
I just showed up.
Just turn on the lights.
all right? [shrieking]
That's it! That's it!
That's enough! That's enough!
[Johnny]
There's a snake. Dave!
[Dave] Where are you. Ehren?
Ehren.
Ehren! What the fuck?
-Ehren!
-How am I supposed to
even help you. Dave?
Just-- I just need to know
you're there.
-[crackling]
-[screams]
Fuck this!
-[Dave] Ehren!
-Oh. I got a weapon now.
motherfuckers.
I got a weapon.
[Dave] Don't hit me. Ehren.
-No. I got a weapon.
-[Dave] Ehren!
-Don't hit me!
-You fuckin'--
Ehren. don't fuckin'
not answer me!
Ehren. answer me.
-[crackling]
-[Ehren screams]
Ah. fuck! There's a door!
Dave. over here!
Dave. this way!
-Yeah. right. Fuck that door.
-Dave. this way!
Fuck that. There's something
bad over there probably.
No. I promise!
[Dave] No. you don't
know shit.
[Ehren] There's a door I just
opened. I swear to God!
Oh. wow. how convenient.
Come this way.
I swear to God.
-I'm not lying to you.
-[Dave] Fuck that door.
You're on your own then.
fucker.
-[clang]
-[shouts]
Shit!
-[screaming]
-[Johnny laughing]
-[Dave] Ehren!
What the fuck is going on?!
I can't even
I can't even fucking do it.
[Zach] What the fuck is this?
[moans. laughs]
-[traps snapping]
-[yells]
Holy shit!
Motherfuckin'--
-[traps snapping]
-[Zach yelling]
[Johnny. laughing] Oh. my God!
Ow! Fucking bitch!
[Johnny] Keep going
to the right. Bam.
I don't trust you now.
[Johnny] If you got
the fucking--
Bam just got bit.
I got bit. Jeff!
I'm going-- Okay. I'm done
fuckin' with you. okay?
-It's buzzin' over there.
-Here.
I'm done fuckin' with you.
I'm helping you.
'Cause you got--
Bam. you got snakebit.
We gotta get you
medical attention.
Come on. Bam. Come on. buddy.
Let's go. Let's go.
Everyone. I'm done
fucking around!
You gotta let--
You gotta open the door. Okay.
Okay.
[Johnny] You got--
Okay. close it!
No! No! No!
No!
Dude. I'll fuck--
That's it. that's it!
That's it!
It got me! Okay? It got me!
[Johnny] The snake got you?
[Bam screams]
-In the leg and in the ribs.
-In the leg and the ribs?
Please!
Fuck!
I'm gonna have
a cardiac arrest.
[Johnny] Turn on the lights.
Okay. okay.
-Welcome to the set. Bam-Bam!
-Oh. my God.
[Johnny laughing]
Zach. you all right?
-Holy shit!
-[Zach] I crawled through
the fuckin' thing!
I heard Zach
and it sounded like
he was gettin' murdered
in here.
[all laughing]
I thought this was like
the only way to get out.
So I just climbed over it.
and then it broke.
Oh. my God. man.
Did you think there was
a snake in the room?
Fuck. yeah!
-You thought
you were gettin' bit?
-Yeah!
[Johnny] Oh. fuck.
[Bam growls]
-[yells]
-[others laughing]
God!
This whole fuckin' place
is probably rigged.
It is. isn't it?
See. when I come up
with my ideas.
I don't write them down.
I just draw a picture
and fax it to Los Angeles.
I just drew a picture of
a fat-ass and a little guy
with a bungee cord connected.
This is "The Bungee Jump."
[Wee Man]
Are you ready. Preston?
[Preston] Just go. just go.
[Wee Man] Three two one.
[Wee Man shouts]
[others laughing. whooping]
[Bam] Yes! Yes!
Yes. yes! Oh. my God.
-[Ehren] You did it!
-That worked perfect!
[cheering. whistling]
Hello. my name's
Johnny Knoxville.
Welcome to our production
of "The Marionettes."
I smell a Tony. Let's go.
[clapping]
Fade in. Timmy. ten years old.
A pasty. dimwitted
but unlikeable boy.
makes his way through
the town square.
He spots Dolores.
11 years old.
Dolores is pretty.
like an old catcher's mitt.
and only has one nut.
Timmy:
[Ehren] Good morning. Dolores.
I want to take you
to the dance.
but I heard Ugly Jeff
asked you. and I was shocked.
Timmy is hit with
Taser-gun darts.
What?
No. fuck that! No. fuck that!
-[screaming]
-[zapping]
[others laughing]
[Johnny] Don't be mad at me.
Be mad at the narrator.
[Ehren] Stop it!
Fuck you!
Fuck!
[laughing. stammering] Timmy:
Gimme a second.
Adam fuckin' Ray!
[Johnny] Timmy. you're
holding up the play!
How can I win her love?
I sure could use a little
help.
Up in the rafters.
a cute. but soon to be crabby
Cupid appears.
-[Wee Man groans]
-[Ehren] Oh. fuck.
[laughter]
[Ehren] Oh. fuck.
[Adam] Cupid:
Timmy. I'm shocked it took you
so long to summons me.
I'm gonna beat you. Chris.
[Wee Man] Okay! Ah!
Pineapples?
What does pineapples
have to do with Cupid?
Cupid then pulls the bow back
on his love arrow
and shoots Dolores in the eye.
-[yells]
-[others groaning]
Sorry.
I'm not Dolores. man!
[Johnny] Sorry!
-[Adam] Timmy:
-Dolores. you drive me crazy!
I feel like my heart
is going to explode.
[Adam] A large brick
of firecrackers
is duct-taped
to Timmy's chest.
and a very long fuse is lit.
No!
-[Wee Man] Oh. shit.
-No!
[Wee Man shrieks]
[Adam] Timmy's heart explodes
like a cantaloupe.
It's burning me!
-[shrieks]
-[banging]
[Ehren] Oh. fuck!
-[Dave] Oh. shit!
-[Wee Man] What?
[Ehren] Oh. fuck!
[Adam] And then.
our two living actors
take their triumphant
final bows
as Timmy hangs there
lifeless and limp.
The End.
-[Johnny] Yay!
-[cheering]
Two thumbs up.
All right. well. this is
an opportunity
that I'm gonna enjoy.
Mr. Knoxville
Did you choose to host
Fear Factor for the money.
or because it really
turned you on creatively?
-[all laughing]
-Tell the truth!
I It turned me on...
-[strained] ...creatively!
-[electricity crackling]
[laughter]
Keep going. Keep going.
All right. Here we go.
[chuckles]
Poof! I'm an old prick now.
[laughs]
[dance music playing in club]
Hello. ladies!
Hey. grandpa. how you doin'?
Good! How you doin'. baby?
All right!
[upbeat music plays]
[Irving] Wow.
[cheering]
[Irving]
He's got his jim dog out!
How are you ladies
doin' down here?
What you gon' do.
watch it or watch us?
I came to watch you girls.
[laughs]
You ladies are going to get
all worked up
and then hopefully
old Irving can swoop in there.
-What's your name?
-[laughs]
Irving.
Maybe some of these ladies'll
want a serving of Irving.
if you know what I'm sayin'.
[announcer] If you ready for
the next entertainer.
then somebody say. "I am!"
I am!
He's harder than a horseshoe!
I'm pretty loose right now.
but I could
probably get it goin'.
[woman]
[Irving]
She wants to see mine?
I'll show her mine right now!
I'm gonna go. I'm gonna.
I'm gonna walk the red carpet.
Yeah. I'm gonna shake it!
[upbeat music continues]
[announcer] I don't know
what the fuck is goin' on.
[club-goers gasping. cheering]
[announcer]
No. he is not gonna stay.
[laughter]
[cheering continues]
I'm Bam Margera.
And I feel like kicking
my dad's ass all day today.
Come on. Bam.
No. I gotta go
to work. jerk-off!
Stop it!
Come on. I gotta go
the hell to work on time!
-Will you stop?
-[thud]
[Johnny] Should I be naked
like the dummy?
As long as you'll
strap me in. I'll do it.
[rocket technician]
Five. four. three. two. one!
[Steve-O] Oh. shit.
-[Bam] Oh!
-[laughter]
[laughs]
-[Bam] Oh. my God!
-[Johnny] Oh. my God.
Yeah. I guess I will have to
hold on like a motherfucker.
[laughter]
[Johnny] Oh. my God.
that's crazy!
[Chris] Oh. please.
It's weird to
strap a dummy to a big rocket
and then see it go off
[imitates rocket]
and then say. "All right.
time for you to get on. Knox."
[Steve-O] It's moments like
these when you know
Johnny Knoxville is
one gnarly dude.
Dun. da-da-da-dun.
da-da-da-dun
da-da-da-da-da-da-
I'm so glad I'm not
the star of this movie.
[laughs]
[Bam] Knoxville's gonna see
what the moon's
gonna look like.
He is gonna go definitely
60 feet up in the air.
He's gonna get annihilated.
But I don't want to
tell him that.
You're gonna be just fine!
Hi. I'm Johnny Knoxville.
and this is my
"Big Red Rocket."
[rocket technician] Five.
four. three. two. one. go!
[laughter]
[Wee Man]
What the fuck was that?
-[Bam] Whoo!
-[Ryan] Oh. my God.
[Wee Man] Holy shit. dude.
[Steve-O] What? What?
[Johnny] Well. usually.
the rockets fail
backwards and forwards.
I was told.
but there was a rocket
that came out the side.
If it'd been
like right here
that'd been a picture-wrap
on old Knoxville.
[laughs]
And now we're trying it again.
It's rocket launch take two.
I'm scared just watching.
-I know. yeah.
-I want a Lance helmet.
I have full. like. adrenaline.
[laughter]
This isn't the best idea ever.
Yes. it is.
I'm Johnny Knoxville
and I'm going to the moon!
[rocket technician]
Five. four. three. two. one!
Later.
[crew cheering]
Yeah! Yeah!
[Bam] If you're okay.
give us a thumbs-up!
[Chris] He held onto it.
[Dave] That was incredible.
[cheering continues]
[Bam] Totally awesome!
All right. we're having
a little party at the office.
But unfortunately.
Ron's in there
and he's in a terrible mood
because his wife
left him again.
Poor Ron.
We're gonna have to go
cheer him up.
That's right. Let's kill him
with kindness. fellas.
It's party time. boys.
Okay. let's do it.
let's do it.
All right. let's do it.
[Poopies]
Let's go cheer up Ron.
Hey. Ron. what do you say?
We'll just have a little cake
and fun in here?
Hey. Ron.
I heard about the breakup.
[Johnny] Yeah.
-[screams]
-[laughter]
Fucking Ron!
Hey. Ron. come on--
Ow! Shit. Ron!
Ow!
I will fucking call HR.
[Jasper] Ow!
Oh. that was my arm!
I'm starting to think
he's racist.
[laughter]
Ron can smell
his wife's cheap perfume
all over Jasper.
and he's furious.
[Jasper] Ron. it's cool.
[Poopies] Oh. no!
Wellthat solves
the office mystery
about who fucked Ron's wife.
[laughter]
[exhales]
[sighs]
-I'm Steve-O. Oh. fuck!
-[laughter]
Oh. why do I have
to be Steve-O?
I'm Steve-O
and this is "Tee Ball."
[breathes heavily]
-[grunts]
-[laughs]
I remember seeing the footage
of the "Box Down Stairs"
when
right after it was shot.
in the editing room. and
I always wondered why
it wasn't allowed to be on TV.
and then I found out
that it was too imitate-able?
[Johnny] Yeah.
Duh.
Yeah. I got
two herniated discs
because of the
"Box Down Stairs." [laughs]
We put a pillow in there.
or two.
Yeah. thank you.
Thanks for those pillows.
-[laughs]
-Oh. man. it killed!
[Greg] You need one
for his head.
[Jeff] All right.
just tuck your head down.
[laughs]
[Johnny]
Let's hurry up and do this!
[Jeff] No worries.
we're getting it taped up.
[Greg] Can you breathe?
[Johnny] Not well.
[Jeff] All right. let's go.
You ready?
[Johnny grunts]
-Oh! Oh.
-[laughter]
[Jeff] Get it back up.
[Greg] Wait. is this the top
or the bottom?
Oh. [chuckles]
[Dave] You okay?
[chuckles] No. I'm not.
That really hurt.
I wanna see a playback.
[Jeff] At one point.
it just took off.
like you
actually got airborne.
In the first Olympics.
they performed naked.
-Oh. yeah.
-And
we would like to do. uh.
one of the events
from the first Olympics.
the high jump.
and if you would do it
buck naked.
-Okay. [chuckles]
-[laughs]
[Johnny]
And you know how they do it.
They kinda run at it
and then they kinda turn?
[Chris] Yeah. yeah.
Fosbury flop.
[Johnny]
Yeah. the old Fosbury flop.
-Yeah.
-I think it's Dick Fosbury.
-Oh. is that who invented it?
Yeah. and now we got
Big Dick Fosbury.
ol' Chris Pontius.
-[breathes heavily]
-[skin slapping]
I'm Chris Pontius.
and this is the "Pole Vault".
Wait. I fucked up my rhythm.
[laughter]
-[exhales]
-I'm Chris Pontius.
and this is the "Pole Vault."
Ah. I totally fucked up.
[laughter]
[Jeff] We need to get some
clean sound of this.
Get in close.
-Get in there.
-Yeah. I got it.
All right.
the Tahitian Dancer.
[breathes heavily]
Detroit Muscle Rock.
[laughter]
I'm Chris Pontius.
and this is the "Pole Vault."
-[breathes heavily]
-[laughter]
[Rachel] Yes. Chris.
[Steve-O] Whoo-hoo!
[cheers] Yea-- Oh!
[Zach] Almost
You started jumping
from too far back.
I know.
I completely fucked up.
Oh!
My angle was all wrong.
[cheering]
[triumphant music playing]
[Johnny] That was amazing.
[Bam exhales] Here comes Dunn.
[chuckles]
[explosion]
[laughter]
No fucking way. dude!
We just spent so much time
getting ready.
-Is there blue on me?
-[laughs]
I'm so happy.
There's a lot of blue.
Dude. that thing goes.
[Johnny laughs]
[Bam] What's the word on. uh.
"Butt X-ray"?
There you go again.
Everyone's fuckin' saying
to me I'm gonna do something
I fucking never said
I was gonna do. You know?
I didn't fuckin'
commit to that.
[Ryan]
What do they want you to do?
They want me to fucking start
shoving shit up my ass!
[Bam] I thought that was--
That wasn't your idea?
No. it wasn't my idea.
I mean. I was always
entertained by the idea.
I never fuckin said
I'd do it. You know?
[Bam]
So you're not doin' that.
Fuckin' highly doubt it.
You know?
And if there's
a fuckin' problem with that
then maybe
someone else can start
shoving shit up their ass.
You know?
Now. I'm lubing up
[Jeff]
I can't see the car. Ryan.
the little toy car
because I'm going to
put it in my butt.
[laughter]
[Bam]
Just shove it the fuck up.
[Ryan] Oh. fuck.
[Steve-O] Oh. fuck. no!
Dude. it feels
so goddamn gross.
[laughter]
Really. You know what?
I'm really questioning
myself right now.
[Jeff] Is it almost in?
[Ryan] It's in. dude.
-[Manny] It's in?
-Yeah.
-[Manny] Let's go.
-Oh. fuck!
I feel like I have to
shit my ass.
[laughter]
Oh. fuck.
I'm not too excited
about this skit.
It's not my favorite
I've ever done.
because there's
a toy car in my butt.
But this is the "Butt X-Ray."
I think I need an X-ray.
-[receptionist] Antoine?
-[Dr. Antoine] Yes?
How you doing?
Pretty good.
-I'm Ryan. and this--
-What can I do for you?
I was partying last night
with some frat guys.
I passed out.
I must've fallen down
and broken something
'cause I haven't been able
to walk right since.
We're gonna take X-ray now
-Okay.
-to be sure.
-We'll take a look.
-Okay.
This is comfy.
[radiologist]
Hold your breath. Don't move.
[whirring]
[doctor 1] Oh. wow!
[doctor 2]
What's that? What you got?
[doctor 1] What is that?
[doctor speaks Spanish]
[laughs]
-[doctor 2] What the hell?
-[doctor 1] A car?
[Jeff] What is that?
[doctor 2]
Is his own car. no? The toy.
-The toy car.
-[Dr. Antoine] Toy car?
[doctor 2] This is the wheel.
See that?
[in Spanish]
What's that?
[Ryan] I have no idea.
That's not part of you.
That's something extra.
I woulda known if I ate that.
No. you won't be able
to swallow that.
That is a car toy.
[Ryan] Well. how did
a car toy get there?
Maybe you stuck it
up your ass.
I didn't stick anything
up my ass.
[Jeff] God. Have you ever seen
anything like that?
No. I've never seen
that in there.
I've seen
the toy car all over.
but no.
never in somebody's rectum.
[Ryan] You can't get it out?
You don't have--
No. I I'm a physician.
But I practice this.
X-ray only.
[Ryan] You think maybe I can
just you know. poop it out?
You won't be able
to poop it out.
In fact. it will hurt you.
In fact. I
I don't think it's even good
for you that you poop it out.
[Jeff] What will happen
if you take Ex-Lax?
Will that help?
No. if he takes Ex-Lax.
he gets a Iot of diarrhea.
but no car.
-[doctor 3] It's up there?
-[laughter]
He must drink a lot.
[Ryan] I mean.
don't show it to everybody.
Yeah.
I appreciate it.
Thank you
for taking care of me.
-Okay.
-Thanks again.
I gotta see it!
[laughter]
[Chris]
It's still in your ass?
[Ryan]
Yeah. we gotta go to the hotel
and pull this thing out.
-[Johnny] Ooh.
-[Ryan] Oh!
Hit! Good.
[Preston groans]
Hello. my name is
Johnny Knoxville.
Welcome to the "Dum Dum Game:
Part Deux."
-aka "Double Boom."
-[all laughing]
In this competition.
our four competitors
and our special guest star.
Paul Walter Hauser.
are going to sit
in this hot seat
and answer trivia questions.
Everyone ready to get started?
[Larry]
Let's raise Zach.
All right.
He's an angel.
Oh. boy.
there's the double boom.
What the fuck?
Jasper. take a seat.
-[groans]
-Yeah. Jasper. let's go!
[Johnny] All right. Jasper.
Where was your father.
Dark Shark. born?
Fuck. [laughs]
What?! I mean. what?
Dude. I'm trying
to give you a softball.
Just drop him!
I'm guessing like Crenshaw.
Venice area?
South Central.
[all exclaiming]
Jesus Christ. Jasper!
It's all the same thing!
That's shameful. You should
-be embarrassed.
-Really. Jasper?
Okay. what is Jeff's
last name. our director?
Dickhead.
No. Tremaine. Tremaine.
God. just get outta the chair!
[all laughing]
Yes. Jasper!
Paul. you realize
you've already
broke into show business.
right?
[all laughing]
[Johnny] You don't need
to be doing this.
This is like a Make-a-Wish.
if it were a punishment.
I've seen worse asses. Zach.
I'm just sayin'.
-Thanks.
-Okay.
[Larry]
[Johnny] How many Earths
could fit inside
our blazing sun?
If you need to phone-a-friend.
you can ask Larry here.
Larry.
[Larry]
Do you know how many Earths
could fit inside of the sun?
[Larry]
Oh. Larry!
Fuck off. Larry.
I'm gonna say seven.
-Oh. you fucked that up.
-I'm gonna say seven.
One point three million.
[Larry]
Oh. boy.
Poopies! Come on.
Thank God I'm not last.
Well
I don't think there is a last.
It keeps going
round and round.
-Yeah. dummy.
-Yeah.
Dude. are you dumb?
Ehren
your face is ugly. so just--
Ooh!
Wow. sick burn!
Oh. it smells.
How many colors
make up the classic rainbow?
Blue. yellow.
orange. green. purple
Red
And
You got this. Poopies.
White.
[laughing]
Oh. my God. Lower it!
Oh. my God. Oh. my God.
Let me just--
Wait. that's gotta
move over a little more--
Sorry. I just had to
shift it over a little.
Oh. my God.
-Okay.
-[laughing]
[Johnny] Poopies what color
are the shoes I'm wearing?
-I can't see.
-[all laughing]
[Wee Man] Don't look!
-[Johnny] What color
are the shoes I'm wearing?
-Red.
Wow!
Ehren's up!
-Zach. you good?
-Oh. yeah. I'm great.
This sucks. dude.
What the fuck?
[exclaiming]
-Oh. my-- Oh. God.
-[Johnny] Oh. Jesus.
-[gagging]
-[Johnny] Please do not puke.
-Stop it!
-[Larry]
-[all laughing]
-[gagging]
[Johnny] Okay. Ehren.
-Who starred in and wrote
-[gags]
"The Meter Fairy"?
I'm the Meter Fairy.
That's-- That would be
Ehren McGhehey.
Danger Ehren. Me.
All. Final answer.
And that is the worst bit
we've ever filmed.
That's not cool. man!
-[screaming]
-[all exclaiming]
Up. up. up. up. up! Up!
[gagging]
[coughing. gagging]
Wait!
-[groans]
-[all laughing]
We gotta give it up
to Zach for sure. dude.
[Johnny] Yay. Zach!
That is it for the
"Dum Dum Game: Part Deux."
Some of my favorite bits are.
like.
ones that just. there's--
Like. we're sittin' around.
we don't have anything to do.
Then someone says.
"Go get some Super Glue".
It's kinda like what happened
with Brad Pitt.
-[laughing]
-He was there
to shoot "Night Monkey".
and you're like. "Why don't
we just kidnap you?"
And he said. "Okay."
And we had
the presence of mind
to call the police department
to let them know
to disregard 9-1-1 calls
about Brad Pitt
being kidnapped.
[laughs]
"I know this just sounds
really specific.
but Brad Pitt's
gonna be kidnapped."
-[laughing]
-"But it's a joke."
"Yeah. it's a joke.
That would never happen."
Hi. I'm Brad Pitt
and I'm gonna get abducted.
[Brandon] All right. good.
See you out there.
Fun with celebrities.
Yo. Brad Pitt!
No shit!
No shit! No. it's Brad Pitt!
Oh. how's it goin'. dude?
-It's slow.
-All right. all right.
Take a break. man.
Yeah. but can I
get your autograph?
-Come on. man.
-Yeah. get him. now! Get him!
-Get in the fuckin' car!
-What are you doing?!
-Holy shit.
-Wait!
[Brad] Hey. hey! Help!
Help! Help! Help! Help!
[onlooker] Hey.
what are you doing to him?
-Leave him alone.
-Go. go. go!
[Brad screaming]
[man in line] Son of a bitch.
[Bam] Oh. shit!
[Chris] Look at him.
-[all laughing]
-Aw. fuck!
[Bam] Yeah.
It's like a drug. yeah.
[Brandon] Run the lights.
You get the license plate?
Shit. someone call the cops.
-Was that Brad Pitt?
-Yeah.
What just happened?
What the fuck?
Brad Pitt got kidnapped.
Yeah. yeah. it was Brad Pitt?
-You see the [indistinct]
-Brad Pitt. he was here?
Brad Pitt was in line
and he was just
kidnapped
and thrown into a van.
I'm really not kidding.
Some dude was like
grabbing my ass.
trying to rip me
outta the car.
He was really
fighting to not get in. too.
Yeah. totally.
-You're a good actor. dude.
-[Brad] Oh. thanks. Chris.
[all laughing]
Hi. I'm Johnny Knoxville
and I'm gonna
get hit by a car real soon.
[engine revving]
All right. guys. we've got
Tory Belleci from MythBusters.
So I've decided to try a trick
for the first time ever.
And frankly. I'm pretty
nervous about it. okay?
Are you ready?
[exhales]
[gulps]
[grunts]
[grunting. gasping]
-[Johnny] Oh. no.
-[grunts]
-[Johnny] Ugh.
-[Steve-O grunting]
On the table. We might be
playing table tennis.
[all laughing]
[Johnny] Wait. wait. wait.
Can you?
-[all laughing]
-You got this?
[groaning]
He's at five centimeters.
[all laughing]
-[groaning]
-Oh. he's crowning!
Maybe you should've
put the ping-pong ball
up your ass
and then puked it out.
[strained] I'm gonna get it.
I'm gonna get it.
I don't know.
this myth might be busted.
[all laughing]
Okay. here's the thing. guys.
I put the ping-pong ball
in my mouth. right?
Yeah.
-Pretending to swallow it.
-Yeah.
But I had already jammed
a ping-pong ball up my ass.
Now I think I lost it.
Oh. God.
A good magician
never reveals his tricks.
-Yeah. right.
-[groaning]
It's our last day of filming
after 25 years
and we haven't learned
a goddamn thing.
-[all laughing]
-[groaning]
Push!
Oh. yuck!
Oh. my God.
[all groaning. exclaiming]
[Johnny]
That was a dirty trick!
[Steve-O] Take it.
That wasn't even. you didn't
even get close to the target.
Oh. no!
Get the dog.
Go. buddy. Go. buddy.
[Jasper]
He heard the ball falling.
-You guys stay.
-Oh. my God!
It fuckin' worked.
[all laughing]
That is all cheese. no whiz.
This is all flour
for our friend Bam.
We're gonna antique him
when he gets here.
-Okay.
-Walkin' in.
-He's walkin' in?
-There he is. walking in.
-What's up?
-What up?
[chuckles]
Not much. How you been?
-Good.
-High five!
[all laughing]
Oh. my God.
That was the best one so far.
You guys.
you kicked my fucking ass.
You got--
[Johnny] He got antiqued!
[Bam]
I was so not ready for that.
[Dave]
That was so good. You went--
Oh. good morning. man.
-Good morning. Bam.
-Howdy.
-Oh. shit.
-Goddamn.
You know. we have that
the
it looks like a dog--
a shock collar for
-The Taser?
-for the neck?
-There's one for your cock?
-Yeah
Poopies said he wants
to try to see if it shocks.
I didn't say. but I will.
I didn't say.
[Johnny]
Oh. I thought you said it.
You were. like.
"Yeah. that'd be awesome."
[chuckling]
When did I say that?
You said--
Yeah. you said. "Sick!"
Can someone go get the. uh
shock collar for your penis?
Yeah. I'll run and get it.
Excuse me.
for Poopies's penis.
Okay. it's on there.
It looks like his dick's
on house arrest.
[all laughing]
[Johnny]
I don't know why we decided
to film this
on the side of a cliff.
Hi. I'm Poo-- [screams]
-[Johnny] Wait! I'm sorry!
-Fuck!
-Poopies. I'm sorry.
-No. I'm not doing this!
-No. come on. Poopies!
-I gave you an opportunity!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
One more time.
One more time. I won't do it.
I'm Poopies
and this is "The Balance Beam
with a Taser on My Dick."
[Jasper] He's gonna
score a T-in-and-out.
[Dave] Gonna make it
all the way across.
[screams] Oh. fuck!
You're supposed
to land on the beam.
[Johnny] You gotta
take your hand off the beam.
Hang on.
[screaming]
-Oh. fuck!
-[all laughing]
I'm fuckin' done. I'm done.
I can't even think about
anything else
but my dick right now.
Ditto.
[laughing]
-Fuck!
-[Johnny]
I didn't even shock you.
-What happened?
-My mind's getting' to me.
-His mind and spirit.
-[all laughing]
That would be a first.
That would be the first time
that's ever happened.
-[Rachel] Yeah. Poops.
-You got this. Poops.
[Jasper]
Come on. Balance it. baby.
[Rachel] You're so graceful.
-[screaming]
-[all laughing]
[Dave] Dude. you almost
rolled down that cliff!
[Jasper] Dave saved you.
[Jeff] Jump out.
[groaning. laughing]
The last movie. Danger Ehren
was all-the-way MVP.
The movie before that. 3D.
Ryan Dunn was MVP.
I feel like I've had
some strong moments
in all of our installments.
but I don't think
I could ever claim
that I was really. like.
the MVP of one.
And when I learned that
there was gonna be
another chance.
I wanted desperately to
step up and just do the thing.
Yeah. I showed up to work
for this one. man.
And the bar's been
pretty high.
But. uh I'll tell ya this.
my butthole really hurts.
[laughing]
When you reach our age.
you gotta get a colonoscopy.
and that begins
with drinking this stuff
that completely
flushes you out.
If you're not 50 and don't
know. it's a super laxative.
In just a few minutes. we're
gonna be pooping violently.
while testing ourselves
with a game of dexterity.
flexibility and stuff.
Game of "Human Pretzel".
But thank God we have
these awesome fashions.
to give you
an inside look at the action.
People don't got
a lot of faith in you
that you're not puking
in this bit. Lance.
No? Not gonna happen?
All right.
Shall we play?
Steve-O will go first. okay?
Right hand. orange.
Right there.
I'm right in
the line of fire right here.
[Rachel]
Chris. left foot. purple.
Sorry. Preston.
-[onlookers groaning]
-[Ehren] Yeah.
[Chris]
Oh. wow. that's very brave.
[Johnny] Oh. I think
she spun it
and said.
"Chris. uh. right foot. pink."
-[Chris] Fucking--
-[Johnny] Yeah. yeah.
[Chris] Oh. look right into
the eye of the storm.
[all laughing]
Okay. left foot. purple.
It's gonna be left foot
brown. real soon.
What's wrong. Lance?
Lance is getting sick.
-[Rachel]
Steve-O. left foot. pink.
-[Johnny] Oh. man.
[all exclaiming]
[Wee Man] Dave!
[Rachel] You guys
are doing great.
We got a leaker!
-Uh-oh.
-Steve-O's--
Oh. God!
Oh. my God.
[Poopies] Dave.
look to the right.
[all exclaiming]
[Jasper] Look at him.
[Chris] Ew. gross!
[Chris]
[all gagging]
[Rachel] Right hand. green.
[Johnny] Goddamn it.
she said right hand. green!
[gagging. retching]
[Ehren] Fuck this!
Oh. my God!
[Johnny] How you doing. Lance?
Still hanging in there?
[Johnny laughing]
-I've never
smelled poop that bad.
-No.
Oh. my God!
Oh. my-- He's still shi
-Oh. my God.
-[people retching]
[Johnny] How did you not puke?
Steve-O is the winner
-[Rachel] Yeah. Steve-O!
-of the Human Pretzel!
-He's coming right now. Okay.
-Oh. God. Get outta here.
[Poopies] Go right up
and shower. Steve-O. shower.
Good job. bubba!
[indistinct chatter]
Don't say anything.
Hey. what can I get you
to drink?
[Wee Man] Two Budweisers.
[bartender] Thank you. dear.
Cheers.
-Cheers.
-Boop!
[bartender]
So. what's crackin'?
[Wee Man] I don't know.
go down
to the beach or something.
Terra!
All right.
What the fuck you doing?
Who the fuck are you?
-Shh.
-Who are you?
-Calm down.
-I'm her freakin' boyfriend.
asshole!
That's cool. bud.
I'm her man-friend.
Dude. don't push me.
Don't push me.
-I'm not even touching you.
-Whoa. Poppy. calm down.
You know. fuck both of you!
Fuck both of you.
So. he and I are kind of
taking a break and
Hey. he's right in here.
-What's up?
-Fuck you!
-Fuck you.
-Yeah. I told you
to get the fuck away.
Don't push him. man!
Stop! Stop!
Get him. Pop! Get him. Pop!
[thug] Get his ass down. man!
[male patron] Come on. guys.
break it up.
Police!
Get on the fucking ground!
Get on the ground!
Freeze!
Everybody up against the wall!
-This is your fuckin' fight.
-Up against the wall!
-Get the fuck off me!
-Damn!
-The fuck are you doing?
[police officer]
Get him up! Get him up!
Freeze. motherfucker. get
your hands behind your back!
-[security] What's going on?
-[Wee Man] Let's go. baby.
Fucking get off me!
[paramedic]
Code 54! Paramedic!
[boyfriend] Get off me!
Paramedic!
[boyfriend]
Get the fuck off me!
-Shut up.
-[boyfriend] Get 'em off me!
Get the fuck off me!
Shut up!
-Shut up!
-Oh. look at them two.
Rick?
-Whoa!
-Oh. shit.
What? He can walk?
Okay.
[patrons whooping]
What was that all about?
What the hell
was all that about?
[cameraman] What happened?
I don't know what happened.
Hello. I am
Johnny the Magnificent.
Today. I'm going to wow you
with my supreme skills
of prestidigitation.
[metal clanking]
Oh. fuck! Oh. God! [yelps]
-What a-- Oh. shit.
-[bull grunting]
Oh. shit. [yelps]
[screams]
[Chris] Oh. my God.
You okay. Johnny?
Holy shit.
[Johnny groans]
[onlooker whooping]
Abracadabra.
[Ehren] You left your hat
out there.
[Johnny] Did we get it?
[Jeff] Take two?
I hate take two with bulls.
-[Dave] Oh. man.
-[Wee Man] We saw Knox
dancing around with the bull.
But we know the hit
that the bull gave Knox
wasn't the one Knox wanted.
It was close.
but it wasn't the one.
[Johnny] What do you think?
Maybe a take two?
Fuck that.
[bull bellowing]
[metal clanging]
This one's twice the size!
Oh. my God. dude.
Oh. shit. Oh. shit!
I don't wanna fuckin'
watch this. man.
[Jeff] All right. are we good?
Hello.
I'm Johnny the Magnificent.
Today. I'm going to wow you
with my supreme skills
of prestidigitation.
-[metal clanging]
-Oh. shit!
-[bull bellowing]
-[Johnny shouting]
[onlooker whoops]
Oh. no. Oh. shit.
[bull bellows]
[others gasping]
[Steve-O] Jesus. Mary.
That one works. That works.
-[Steve-O] Damn.
-Johnny. you okay?
P.J.. talk to me. You okay?
You all right?
[Jasper] He's had it.
[Jeff] You doin' okay?
Johnny?
[Preston] He's getting' back.
He's coming to.
[Eric] He's comin' back. yeah.
[Jeff] You all right?
That was a violent brawl.
One-sided to be sure.
[chuckles]
[Wee Man]
Fucking gnarly. dude.
-[Steve-O] Yeah.
-Did we get it. Jeff?
[Jeff] We got exactly
what you wanted.
-[Wee Man] Yeah. Knox!
-Yeah. Knox!
[Johnny] Oh. fuck.
So what happened
after it hit me?
[Jeff] Dude. it's gnarly.
This is you. this is the bull.
[all laughing]
[Wee Man] He didn't even
mess around. dude.
He turned around
and just nailed him.
[Steve-O]
Dude. that was insane.
[Poopies] Yeah. Knox.
[Ehren] It's probably the
biggest hit you've ever taken.
[Chris] And that's why
he is the captain.
[Johnny] That bull
didn't like fuckin' magic.
[laughter]
[Poopies]
Yeah. Knox. we love you!
-[clapping. cheering]
-[Johnny] Love you!
[Poopies] Captain!
[Steve-O]
Concussions aren't great.
But as long as you have 'em
before you're 50. it's cool.
And Knoxville is 49.
So we're good.
Hello. I'm Johnny Knoxville.
and this is
the "Escape Room from Hell."
[laughs]
[Johnny] There are
three different rooms.
You have to solve puzzles in
each room to get to the next.
Godspeed.
[sighs] Thanks. dude.
[Johnny. over speaker]
All right. Wee Man
To get to the next room.
you'll have to reach
through that wall
to find
a special Jackass coin.
-I don't know--
-Fuckin' hold my hand and go.
Go! Fuckin' put it in there!
-I don't wanna hold your hand.
-Go!
[screaming]
What the fuck! Okay.
What the fuck is that?
-[laughs]
-What the--?
What's the deal?
What's it feel like?
-I don't know!
-[Ehren] This sucks.
-I can't tell.
-[Ehren] Doggone it.
I put my hand in it
and I feel shit.
[Dave] I saw you
put your hand in it.
[all laughing]
-Dave! Dave!
-Come on. Dave.
-Oh. my God. dude.
[Johnny] Get in there. Dave.
-[Wee Man] Scoop. Scoop.
-[Dark Shark] Reach down.
All-- Put your arm
all the way in and go down.
[Wee Man]
Go in and down. In and down.
-[Zach] What the fuck?
-[shouting. laughing]
[Zach] Oh. God!
There you go. Got it?
It's a. it's a butthole!
[Wee Man screams]
Oh. my God!
My finger went in it.
[all laughing]
[Preston] Oh. God.
it's really good.
-[Johnny] Get that coin.
-Okay.
[Johnny] You gotta reach in
deep and scoop.
[Ehren] Dude. go deep.
[Zach] Is it in your butthole?
[groans]
[Johnny]
Oh. they got the coin!
-[Dave] Oh. my God.
-[Johnny]
They got more than the coin.
-[Dark Shark] What the fuck?
-[Dave] Dude. my finger--
I jammed my finger backwards.
I can smell the shit
on your hand.
Looks like you guys
solved the puzzle.
I think we're moving
to the next room.
[laughs]
Okay. Dave.
this next puzzle is for you.
And what's gonna happen to me?
Well. if you solve
the puzzle. nothing.
You have to correctly guess
four animal sounds
to stop this. To save Dave.
Are we ready?
Wait. you're goin' heel?
Yeah. heel.
-Okay!
-Oh. shit.
No. dude. Oh. my God.
What sound does a dog make?
[barking]
Okay. good job.
What sound does a cat make?
[meowing]
Wow.
they're doin' really good.
What sound
does an aardvark make?
[quacks]
No.
No. they don't make a sound!
They don't sound.
Okay. okay. okay.
-I got that right! [laughs]
-[Wee Man] Nice!
Yeah. baby!
[Johnny]
You just need one more.
Dude. are you kidding me? No.
[Johnny] What sound
does a cassowary make?
-No!
-[Ehren] Cassowary?
[grunting]
That's incorrect!
[Dark Shark] Oh. shit.
-[Johnny] That's incorrect!
-[Wee Man]
Just start sayin' shit!
[Dave screaming]
[Johnny laughing]
[Ehren] Oh. my God!
[all shouting. laughing]
Goddamn. bro!
Dude. what the fuck?
[Dave whimpering]
That is correct! That is
the sound a cassowary makes.
And I think
we can go to the final room.
It's done. dude.
Dave. it's done.
Dude.
my dickhead's just going
[imitates machine]
[all laughing]
[Johnny]
In this bit. Ehren will sit
in this comfy electric chair
that we built for him.
-[Ehren] Wait. what?
-You have
all these jumper cables.
You have to get
the right jumper cables
on the right thingies.
Then you come up here
and you turn this down.
How do we know
if we got the right ones?
Because if you
don't have the right ones.
Ehren is going to get shocked.
[Chris] Have you ever done
an escape room?
Fuck no and fuck that shit.
You do it?
-I have done it.
-You've done an escape room?
Yeah.
-I don't believe you.
-It's a team-building exercise.
[Johnny laughs]
All right. Ehren.
get in your love seat.
[Dave] She's the worst
at doing it.
[Johnny] Let's close the doors
and please start the game.
Just give him
a little shock now.
-Ow! Fuck!
-[crackling]
[Johnny] Hey. hey. Hey. guys.
I'm sorry. that was a mistake.
-[Wee Man] Fuck!
-That was a mistake.
-Fuck that!
-[Ehren] Fuck. dude.
[laughs]
-[Dave] Fuck this.
-[Johnny]
You guys can start now.
Fuck. what are we doing?
-Here's seven.
-This one's four.
-Four?
-Yeah. where's seven?
I don't know where four is.
Fuckin' figure it out.
you guys!
-Where two at?
-Two's right here. The red one.
[Johnny]
You guys are getting close.
-[Dark Shark] Where's four?
-Oh. no. wait!
[Dark Shark] Get that
last one right there.
-[Johnny]
Are they all in place?
-Damn it.
-Okay. whoa. whoa. whoa
-Calm down.
-I think it's colors.
-No! It's numbers.
-He had it wrong.
-No. it's fucking
not numbers. guys!
He had it wrong
and he put it up there.
-Okay. do the thing!
-He's gonna get shocked!
[Wee Man]
No. he's not. No. he's not.
-[crackling. buzzing]
-[screaming]
[Dave] I knew it! I knew it!
[Wee Man] Okay! Okay!
-It was right!
-I turned it off!
-Turn it off!
Turn it off. Turn it off.
Okay!
Y'all killed him. man.
-Y'all killed him. bro!
-Fuck. dude.
-he's like fuckin' dead. dude.
-All right. Dave.
Get the thing. Get him out.
-Get him out. Get him out.
-[Dave] He's out.
What happened?
-Hey. sit still--
-Get outta here! What the fuck?
It's your hat.
I'm taking your hat off.
Hey.
she's trying to let you out!
[Johnny] Blow the horn.
Who's got the horn?
[horn blows]
[Johnny] That's good.
That's good.
Fuck this fucking shit!
-[horn blows]
-[Ehren] Fuck!
-[Dark Shark]
Damn. that was crazy.
[Ehren] Fuck this fuckin'--
[screaming]
I'm out! Fuck off!
Oh. my God.
Well I think that's it
for the Escape Room from Hell.
[laughs]
-Wait-- We're done?
-[Jeff] Yep.
-Oh. my God.
-We did it.
You got out
of the escape room!
Do we get a therapist
after this shit. man?
-Do we get a therapist?
-Good job. Dark Shark.
Goddamn.
you all fucked me up. man!
And you put your hand
in Zach's ass.
-Way. way up his ass. dude!
-[laughing]
[Ehren] Fuck you guys!
[Jeff] You forgot your shoes!
[Ehren]
Fuck this fuckin' place!
There were headlines
on the internet
that you said
this Jackass film
will be the last one ever.
After you said that about
every single Jackass movie.
do you think anyone's
gonna take that seriously?
As much as I fuckin' hate
to say it
-[sighs]
-[laughs]
[Poopies] Don't say it!
I'm getting emotional.
[chuckles]
[Poopies] Don't.
It it is.
That's it.
[wind whistling]
["My Way" playing]
Hello. I'm Johnny Knoxville!
And this is the end!
[all] Yeah!
[laughing]
[song ends]
[cheering. laughing]
["We'll Meet Again" playing]
[Wee Man] Yeah! Yeah!
Oh. my God
-[explosion]
-What the fuck?
[chattering]
[laughs]
[groans]
[chattering. laughing]
-God. it feels so good!
-Yeah.
I can finally
put my clothes back on.
[Steve-O] I need money
to stop in the hospital.
[grunts. laughs]
All right. come on!
-[cheering]
-Yeah. A group photo.
-Yeah. Poopies. Antidope.
-Right here. bro.
I think Poopies is crying.
-[Chris] What's wrong?
-This might be the last bit
we ever film. [crying]
[Dark Shark]
Nah. you ain't like this.
No. I think
he's actually upset.
[interviewer]
So. what's it like
seeing all this old footage?
Everyone looks like babies.
Actually.
I feel old and I miss Dunn.
[Johnny]
Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah.
I feel old and I miss Dunn.
[inaudible]
[cameraman]
What are we doing here?
Steve-O's late for his plane.
so I'm gonna wake him up.
-Okay.
-Make sure he makes it.
[laughing]
[screams]
[cheering]
Steve-O!
-[Poopies] Spike.
-[Johnny] Love ya. buddy.
[Johnny] Spike Jonze!
Jeff Tremaine over there!
[crew member] John!
Hey. will you get him
back to his room?
-[Poopies] So good.
-[Johnny] Who this?
I didn't hear him
on there. so--
-[Jeff] It's. it's for you.
-Hello?
[driver] Loomis.
you're up this way. right?
-[Loomis] Yeah.
-There's trouble?
[inaudible]
[song continuing]
-You did great today. Jeff.
-Stop. God.
-[kisses]
-[groans]
Oh. Johnny Knoxville!
-This is the end!
-[song ends]
-[Jeff] And two.
-[explosion]
-[cheering]
[Wee Man] Ohhh. shit!
[Ehren] Look at that
fuckin' fireball!
[screaming]
["Southerly" playing]
Hello. I'm Johnny Knoxville!
Hi. I'm Johnny Knoxville!
Hi. I'm Johnny Knoxville.
Hello. I'm Johnny Knoxville.
Welcome to Jackass.
[grunts]
[screaming]
[groans]
Shit!
[electricity crackles]
Oh. no!
That's semen. all right.
[retching]
-Did you fart on me?
-Yep.
Oh. my God. no!
[drumming]
-[Preston] Ow!
-[laughing]
Ow!
[laughing]
[cheering]
Phew.
-[buzzing]
-[laughing]
[laughs]
[song ends]
I hate the fact
that I had to fuckin'
hang out with alligators
and fuckin' cobras.
I have dicks branded
on my ass.
Everything fuckin' sucks.
[laughs]
Like everybody's just
effin' with me today.
And my Misfits sock.
["Shine a Light" playing]
[chattering. laughing]
That went good.
[all laughing]
That's something.
[struggling]
-[chattering. laughing]
-Sorry. bro. What happened?
fast.
And then it just. like
-Yeah.
-it just slammed down.
[screams. grunts]
[yells. groans]
[groans]
[barking]
Oh. no!
[laughing]
[groans]
[cheering]
Is Butterbean okay?
[laughing]
-Ow!
-You okay?
Oh. yeah. I feel great.
Good job. man.
[cheering]
[Poopies] All right. boss.
we love you!
[Chris] Love you.
[Poopies] Captain!
-Whoa!
-[laughing]
-Ow!
Oh. my God.
[laughs]
Look how nervous he is.
This sucks. Oh. man.
[thunder crashing]
Spin you around.
[screams]
[shouting]
-[gunshot]
-Ow!
-[laughing]
[screaming]
[laughing]
-I need help.
-Yeah.
[song ends]
But. man. that almost
turned out real bad.
Yeah. I was scared. man.
Shit.
Scariest thing ever. man.
Yeah. that was exactly
what we wanted though.
Oh. God. That is--
It couldn't have ended
any better.
That's-- I don't know if
that's exactly what I wanted.
That's exactly what I wanted.
Yeah.
Reminder.
The stunts in this movie were
performed by professionals.
so for your safety
and the protection
of those around you.
do not attempt any of
the stunts you have just seen.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm